Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Tal'Dorei's kingdoms
lay broken at my feet.
yet my conclave continues to fail me.
Send me. my king.
I will dispatch those that threaten you.
You have your talents.
But with Umbrasyl fallen.
Raishan's mission
is more crucial than ever.
We are not alone.
Something was here.
What?
Oh. gods.
Yes.
My children soon will be gods.
No!
Thordak is becoming irrational.
Insane.
Intent on stripping Tal'Dorei of its gold.
But not to satisfy his greed.
For another purpose.
What purpose?
- Enough of this yappin'!
- Grog. don't!
Okay.
Maybe a little more yappin'.
Everyone in this chamber shares a goal.
The end of the Cinder King.
And if you join me. it is a goal
we are capable of achieving.
We know firsthand what you're capable of.
Your kind razed Byroden.
Nearly everyone in our village dead.
Including our mother.
Not all dragons are the same.
Some can be cruel.
Some can be clever.
But some can be truthful.
Thordak did that to you?
Not exactly.
But he will be punished nonetheless.
So it's revenge you're after.
Not a stranger to vengeance. are you?
Then you know
it can create unusual allies.
So what did he do to you?
Lovers' quarrel?
It's not what Thordak did.
It's what he didn't do.
Trapped in the Fire Plane.
tethered to the soul anchor.
Thordak was a pathetic prisoner of flame.
Until I snuck through Pyrah
to strike a deal with him.
A runic curse afflicts me.
But centuries of survival
have given Thordak knowledge of a cure.
Free me. diseased deceiver.
and I shall free you of your ailment.
The bonds of the soul anchor
were unbreakable.
But with my magic.
he gave himself over to it.
Fused with it.
Its elemental force nourishing his body.
contaminating his mind.
I begged him to use prudence.
But the gem gave him ungodly power.
And uncontrollable rage.
He called himself king.
Demanded I find loyal subjects.
His conclave.
And the cure?
There is no cure.
Then why not slay him yourself?
Your magic made him like this.
With that crystal in his chest.
neither of us can destroy him alone.
But together--
There is no "together." bitch.
You opened that rift.
Half of Pyrah is dead because of you.
I freed him. yes.
He massacred your people. true.
I assume you wish me dead. Ashari?
That's an understatement.
Your wish will soon be granted.
The pain grows worse every day.
But I will see Thordak pay for his lies
before his plan comes to fruition.
Plan. plan-- What plan?
This vague bullshit's getting old.
A new order of elemental dragons
born of his own spawn.
When his brood of eggs in Emon hatches.
your world will be bathed in fire.
My vision.
When will these eggs hatch?
Weeks. Maybe days.
I mean. what are we waitin' for?
We got vesticles--
- Vestiges.
- They whupped Umbrasyl.
Let's charge that castle
- and whup him. too!
- Ha.
You'd be destroyed in a heartbeat.
You may have vestiges
but not the one you need.
The Plate of the Dawnmartyr.
Magical armor
that can repel hellfire itself.
It has felled dragons before.
And it can again.
I don't suppose you brought
this thing with you
in. like. a big purse or. like. a tote?
It resides in Ank'Harel.
Located by Umbrasyl
before you destroyed him.
Now another treasure hunter seeks it.
So time is of the essence.
Raishan. go fuck yourself.
Anyone can conjure illusions.
This is clearly an ambush.
And we are not falling for it.
The answer is no.
You all agree with the Ashari?
We're a team.
Without an alliance. I die.
As do you.
But if that's the path you've chosen--
No. no. don't let her do it.
Kima.
Shaun.
Are you all right?
Waking in your arms again?
Oh. you should start charging me.
Ow.
For the last time. Grog. it's me.
Mm-hmm. Well. then say something
only the real Keeper Yennen would know.
Sometimes you wear a crown
and call yourself
"Grand Poo-bah de Mayonnaise"
when no one's looking.
Yeah. okay. it's her.
Thank the Dawnfather
she only locked you in the dungeon.
It could have been far worse.
The question remains.
Do we dare chase down this armor?
Conspire with Raishan?
No way.
She killed Sovereign Uriel.
It's a deal with a devil.
But how badass would it be
if we rolled in riding a fucking dragon?
Knock-knock. Thordak! Acid!
Uh. she shoots poison.
Oh. Right.
Knock-knock. Thordak!
Poison!
If she helps defeat the conclave.
that's well worth it.
I don't like this. either.
but Raishan could have just attacked us.
She wanted to talk.
Maybe we should listen.
To a mass murderer?
Sometimes a stiff moral code
must be bent for the greater good.
No!
I will not dishonor the Ashari.
I'll go after her.
So. we all going out the window?
Whoever's there.
you don't want to fuck with me tonight.
I don't doubt it.
The idea of working with that monster.
After what she did to my people.
I know.
And the rest of the team.
It always feels like
my opinions don't count.
They count with me.
Do they. Vax?
Y-You've been so...
different.
I miss you.
There were things I needed to understand.
With the Matron.
And do you?
Not everything. But enough.
There's a balance.
Like I'm finally ready for...
whatever comes next.
I'm glad you have someone
who supports you.
Kiki.
I can be that person for you.
if you need me to.
I need that a lot right now.
Sorry. Sorry. Was that bad?
I-I felt your tongue.
and it freaked me out.
and-and I'm-I'm new at this and--
No. no. it was wonderful.
Just... intense.
And. um. I-I need a moment.
Oh. um. okay.
I'll walk back first. then.
so no one suspects.
I'll see you there.
You're up early.
Never slept. I hate our options.
And I hate how it's driving a wedge
between the group.
Bollocks.
What's really bothering you. darling?
When the Briarwoods came.
no one could have prevented it.
But this... I did this.
I had us flee here. and Raishan followed.
I've endangered my people once more.
The way you self-analyze.
I've always admired it.
But at some point.
you have to forgive yourself.
No one can undo the past.
Well. one can certainly try.
You may know me better
than I know myself. Vex'ahlia.
And you're right. I must focus
on the problems ahead.
On fixing this.
Well. not this. This is rubbish.
I know we can.
Together.
Hmm.
Right.
I was thinking. it won't matter
whether Raishan is lying
if we can get to those eggs.
If they're real. we'd have an ally.
And if they aren't--
Then we let our vestiges do the talking.
Shall we wake the others?
Trinket?
Sun Tree. if you can hear me.
grant us luck.
A stealth mission
into a dragon's lair.
You've come a long way
from stealing from my shop.
my handsome half-elf.
Ah. you know. Same game. bigger walls.
The item you requested.
Should make quite a show.
I'd expect nothing less. Shaun.
This feels weird every time.
Hmm.
Whoa. Place looks like shit.
Good to be home.
All right. huddle up.
As we know. I'll be making
a daring aerial incursion.
Which is certain to fail.
I mean. I wouldn't say "certain."
Is highly likely to fail.
I'm sort of with Vex on this one.
Thank you. Stubby.
In any case. you all have
your backup assignments.
Yep.
I'm on rock duty.
Me and Grog will get
up close and personal with our vestiges.
Vesticles.
With mine circling overhead.
I'll be watching Vax.
And I'll be ready
with the signal for when he fails.
If. If I fail.
Sure. brother. Sure.
Plan sounds aces.
What could possibly go wrong?
No!
Shit. shit. Do the thing!
Let's give him a taste of our toys!
♪ Mythcarver ho! ♪
More insects.
Oh. fuck!
A bigger target.
Oi! Thordak!
Come on. We need to rejoin the fight.
No. damn it.
She was right about all of it.
The eggs. the nest.
The vestiges aren't enough.
We need to run.
These are the vestiges
Umbrasyl coveted?
Your relics will lie in ash
with your corpses.
Go! Take cover!
Pike!
We need to hide! Now!
Quickly! In there!
Can't run. can't hide. What do we do?
The arrogance!
That you would dare enter my domain?
- Raishan?
- Careful where you point that.
This is your fault.
You told Thordak we were coming.
Fool. I warned you.
Get us out of here. and we'll reconsider.
Finally. a rational mind.
Come close.
Group hug. Everybody get intimate.
Somebody put out that fire.
I gotcha. Just-- Aah!
Kiki...
Hold still. Try not to move.
Now do you trust me?
Then make haste for Ank'Harel.
You're safe. my progeny.
Safe.
But how did they get that close?
No. it's all right. Shh.
It won't happen again.
For I will have Vox Machina brought to me.
and they shall burn.
Ank'Harel. the Jewel of Marquet.
Also. fun fact. my old stomping grounds.
Over here is the famed Suncut Bazaar.
The River District. where you can find
anything your heart desires.
And I do mean anything.
Ah.
Those fearsome men in uniform
are the Hand of Ord.
Guardians of the mysterious emperex
of this place. J'mon Sa Ord.
And down this street is where
your dragon friend said
we'd find the vestige.
I. uh. don't suppose you want to break in
and steal a priceless relic for us?
Mm. I'm a salesman now. friend.
All your palace intrigue.
no longer intriguing.
If you need me. I'll be sipping
a glass of Stassman down the street.
Ta-ta.
Hey. uh. Gil. if a fella were looking for
a traveling musical act around here.
where would he start?
Where do you think you're going?
Vex. remember that favor you owe me?
All right. we know the drill.
Simple smash-and-grab. Home by supper.
Easier said than done.
It's high noon. There are eyes everywhere.
Then we call it off.
What?
Raishan's holding all the cards.
and we're exactly where she wants us.
Vax?
What other play do we have?
I-I don't know.
But I refuse to believe
that our only two choices
are Raishan or failure.
Keyleth. I--
Percy? That sounded like...
We're not the only ones
who want that plate.
These wounds.
Hey. Stay with me. Who did this to you?
She is still here.
A pepperbox. It can't be.
Percy. we need to keep our heads
if we're going to--
- Right behind you. Percy!
- Wait!
Everyone. get down!
Sorry.
I'll try to stabilize him.
Vex. your broom. Follow them.
I... I gave it to Scanlan.
You what?!
Vax. look out!
Ah. shit. Sorry.
Spice?
Aah! Uh. I'm sorry. what?
You spice? Spice it?
What? Oh.
Uh. I mean. sometime--
No. no. not right now. I'm--
I'm going to see my daughter.
Oh.
Does she spice?
Dude.
Huh?
Dr. Anna Ripley.
Why am I not surprised. Percival?
Then again. you put things together
faster than anyone I've met.
Hand over the vestige.
and I may let you live.
Which one?
Mythcarver was quite handy
before you stole it back.
Ah. you've improved my old prototype.
How flattering.
There's nowhere to run. Ripley.
You're all alone.
Oh. that's the thing. Percival.
I'm never alone.
We had a bargain. Percy.
And I will happily collect.
♪ Do ya spice? ♪
♪ Oh. ah. gotcha. unh! ♪
♪ You wanna spice? ♪
♪ Sexy mama ♪
♪ Oh. get nice with me and spice ♪
Chirp.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm